Guide to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Records, 1975-2021 CTC.2000.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District Development, 1979-2000; II.
  - District Development files, 1979-2000; 1.
    The District Development series includes information regarding the many buildings operated by the Cultural Trust and their plans to improve and revitalize the Cultural District. There is a considerable amount of materials detailing the plans for what would become the O'Reilly Theater, Allegheny Riverfront park, and Theater Square. Also included are materials related to the renovations of buildings along Penn Avenue that are in Cultural District. The materials are arranged in alphabetical order by the title of the folder.* Urban Development Action Grant, Urban Redevelopment Authority.
    - All-Star baseball game initiatives, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny Riverfront Park by Quandel Group Inc, July 1995 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Allegheny Riverfront Project by Turner Pittsburgh, July 1995 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Allegheny Riverfront Project Response to Request for Proposal by Turner Pittsburgh, July 1995 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Archaeology and History at the Seventh Street Site by Verna L. Cowin and Deborah Casselberry and the Carnegie Museum of Natural History, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Archaeological Investigations at the Eighth Street Site by Verna L. Cowin and Deborah Casselberry and the Carnegie Museum of Natural History, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Art Cinema, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Art Cinema and Pittsburgh Filmmakers, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Arts conference - Partners for Livable Places, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Auditorium authority funding, 1984-1992 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Auditorium authority bond calculations, 1990-1994 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Bell Telephone, 1991-1993 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Bridge lighting plan, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Bridgeport Connecticut materials, 1992-1993 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Building history research, 1990-1994 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Century building agreement revised, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Century building agreement revised, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - CNG Tower land rent, 1984-1992 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Combined Proposal Program Management Services and Construction Management Services Seventh and Penn Project and Allegheny Riverfront Park by BRH Builders division of the MacArthur Group, July 6, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Department of Environmental Resources planning module, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Department of Commerce small business assistance program, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Construction Management Services for the Allegheny Riverfront Park by Management Engineering Corporation, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - COMPASS Management and Leasing Inc., 1992 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Conceptual Proposal for Pittsburgh Live at 911/921 Penn Avenue by Entertainment Centers of America Inc. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Construction manager materials, 1992-1993 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Construction Progress Report for the Pittsburgh Regional History Center and Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania by Jendoco Construction Corporation, July 1995 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Cost estimates for office building theater and parking garage, 1991-1994 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Cultural District brochure for the Allegheny Conference on Community Development, September 1987 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Cultural District brochure remake, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Cultural District capital requirements: project costs and funding sources, 1990-1992 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Cultural District: Development Strategy by Buckhurst Fish Hutton Katz Inc., 1987 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Cultural District: Development Strategy by Buckhurst Fish Hutton Katz Inc. draft, 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Cultural District newspaper clippings, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Cultural facilities in Mixed-Use Development by the Urban Land Institute, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Dale Schwab's running club, 1992-1993 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Dead file correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - District development, 1992-1997 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - District development, 1992-1997 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - District development agreement, 1991-1992 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - District development committee, 1985-1988 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - District development committee meeting, November 1988 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - District development committee meeting, September 1994 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - District development fund, 1989-1992 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - District development fund, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - District development fund, 1993-1995 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - District development fund budget, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - District development fund budgeting, 1989-1991 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - District development fund report, September 1994 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - District development fund various, 1992-1995 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Downtown development award, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Downtown management organization, 1989-1994 (Box 106, Folder 2-3)
    - Downtown neighborhood association, 1987-1991 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Duquesne Light, 1991-1993 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Easement agreement materials, 1992-1993 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Edge Architecture (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Equitable Gas, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Equitable Resources proposal for a new corporate headquarters, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Facade renovations - Associated Artists of Pittsburgh, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Factory Outlet Consultants initiative, 1991-1993 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Feasibility Analysis for a Performing Arts District in Pittsburgh Market Study Components by Economic Research Associates and Brannigan-Lorelli Associates, July 1983 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Federated Investors, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Fee Proposal Marketing and Economic Feasibility Penn-Liberty Preservation Study Pittsburgh Pennsylvania by Hammer Siler George Associates, January 1986 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Financial Feasibility Update of the Cultural District Parking Structure by Walker Parking Consultants / Engineers, May 1992 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Financing materials, 1991-1994 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Foundation Investigation Allegheny International Project Site Liberty Avenue at Seventh Street Second Ward City of Pittsburgh Allegheny County Pennsylvania by Engineering Mechanics Inc., December 1984 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Fulton alley repair, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Fulton mural, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Funding proposals and strategies, 1990-1991 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Future Cultural Trust projects, 1986-1988 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Galbreath Company Realtors, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Gap Financing, 1987-1990 (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - Garage development, 1990-1991 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Garage and movie complex, 1990-1992 (Box 108, Folder 2-4)
    - Gateway Environmental Contractors final project log for Wiener World Pittsburgh Cultural Trust, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Gateway Technical building and 7th Street parking lot - complete appraisal of real estate, November 1998 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Ground lease issues, 1989-1991 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Harris Theatre opening, November 1995 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Harris Theatre rental rates, 1997-1998 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Heinz Endowment Cultural District tour, June 1990 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Heinz Hall work invoices, 1986-1988 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Historic district - CLIO Group, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Historic District materials, 1990-1993 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Historic preservation preliminary case report for the Allegheny International and Stanley project volumes 1 and 2, January 1984 (Box 109, Folder 8-9)
    - International center coalition, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - James Murray-Coleman Assistant Director of District Development, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Jendoco Construction Corporation (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Landscaping, 1989-1993 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Liberty Avenue 801-803 construction services proposal by Massaro Company, January 2000 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Liberty Avenue 801-803 Historic Renovation and Redevelopment by L.P. Perfido Associates, October 1993 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Liberty Avenue 801-803 New Pittsburgh Cultural Trust offices by Jendoco Construction Corporation (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Liberty Avenue 801-803 proposal by Rycon Construction Inc. (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Liberty Avenue view of between Eight and Ninth streets photographs (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Limited Feasibility Study and Market Review for the Pittsburgh Trust for Cultural Resources - Heinz Hall and CNG Tower Foodservice by Cini-Little International, June 1986 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Liquor Licenses, 1989-1990 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Legal Issues and Summaries, 1993-1994 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - LPC Penn / Liberty lease, 1987 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Magazine articles on arts districts, 1987-1989 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Management Committee meeting agendas and outlines, 1990-1991 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Market and Financial Feasibility Study by Walker Parking Consultants / Engineers, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Marketing Strategy for the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust by Grubb & Ellis Company, June 1992 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Michael Graves information (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Memorandum of Understanding - draft copies, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Memorandum of Understanding - final, 1992 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Moose Hall facade relocation, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Moose Hall facade relocation photos (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Moose Hall and Stanley Theater - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, 1983-1989 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Movie theater feasibility, 1991-1992 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Movie theater materials, 1990-1995 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - New Carnegie library, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - New Granada theatre Herman O. Watson, 1989-1992 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - New ideas, 1992-1993 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey Center for the Performing Arts, 1990-1993 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Nixon theater photograph collection (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - No Wall Productions (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Penn Avenue 801 information, 1998-1999 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Penn Avenue 900 by Crossgates Inc., May 1997 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Penn Avenue 900 by Crossgates Inc. with notes, May 1997 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Penn Avenue 900 an Adaptive Reuse Proposal by No Wall Productions Development Corporation, May 1997 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Penn Avenue 900 Historic rehabilitation and adaptive reuse - response to request for proposals, May 1997 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Penn Avenue 900 proposed development by Trek Development Group, May 1997 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Penn Avenue 900 proposed evaluations, 1997-1998 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Office / theater / garage project, 1990-1991 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Office / theater / garage project, 1991-1992 (Box 114, Folder 1-4)
    - Office / theater / garage project, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 1-4)
    - Office / theater / garage project architect selection, 1991-1992 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Office / theater / garage project architect finalists' slides, 1990-1991 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Office / theater / garage project Buchanan Ingersoll, 1991-1993 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Office / theater / garage project construction manager selection, 1992-1994 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Office / theater / garage project correspondence from Midge Brogan, 1991-1992 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Office / theater / garage project directory, November 1992 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Office / theater / garage project meeting notes, 1991-1993 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Office / theater / garage project Pittsburgh Public Theater, 1989-1993 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Office / theater / garage project projected financial data, May 1992 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Old parking study revisions, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Operating expense information, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Other cultural developments regional and national, 1988-1992 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Overview of the Current Market and Future Market Projections by Grubb & Ellis, June 1993 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Parking Structure Design - statement of qualifications by Walker Parking Consultants / Engineers, July 1991 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Passenger rail service, 1986-1990 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Budget and Zoning Analysis for Penn Avenue Theater / Office Building by Kingsland Scott Bauer Havekotte Architects, June 1991 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Penn Avenue Office Development by Marguerite Brogan Real Estate Consulting Services, June 1991 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Penn / Liberty Historic District, 1986-1987 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Penn / Liberty Historic District Pittsburgh Section 106 Report by CLIO Group Inc., March 1985 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Penn / Liberty Historic District file catalog by L.P. Perfido Associates Architects, May 1994 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Penn / Liberty Historic District Use of the Existing Structures Code and the Renovation of Single Stair Buildings by L.P. Perfido Associates Architects, December 1992 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Penn / Liberty Historic District Revitalization Proposal by L.P. Perfido Associates Architects, March 1987 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Penn / Liberty holding company, 1987-1990 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Penn / Liberty Preservation Study and Architectural Study by CLIO Group Inc., 1986 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Penn / Liberty Preservation Studies by Kingsland Bauer Havekotte Architects, 1984-1987 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Penn / Liberty Urban Design Study by Llewelyn-Davies Associates, December 1979 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Penrose Development Management Service (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Peters general contractors construction managers contracting engineers (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Phase I Environmental Assessment Report Theater Square Project Pittsburgh Cultural District by Civil & Environmental Consultants Inc., October 1993 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh High School for Creative and Performing Arts, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Plan for the Cultural District by Damianos / GBQC: Associated Architects, November 1988 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Plan for the Cultural District by Damianos / GBQC: Associated Architects, January 1989 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Plan for the Cultural District, 1992 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Playhouse Square Center in Cleveland Ohio, 1988 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary Foundation Investigation Proposed Stanley Theater Addition Penn Avenue & Seventh Street Second Ward Pittsburgh Pennsylvania by Engineering Mechanics Inc., September 1983 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Preservation studies, 1986-1988 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Private document, 1990-1993 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Program account current budget and invoices, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Program account previous invoices (cleared), 1990 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Program Management Services Proposal Seventh and Penn Project by the Gustine Company, July 1995 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Project costs and funding sources, 1990-1992 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Project Manual Façade Renovations Associated Artists of Pittsburgh by Damianos + Anthony Architects, June 1997 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Property information (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Proposal for Construction Management Allegheny Riverfront Park by the Maguire Group Inc, July 1995 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Proposal for Leasing Services Office / Theater Mixed Use Project in the Cultural District by Grubb & Ellis, April 1992 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Proposal for Program Management Services Seventh and Penn Project by the Maguire Group Inc, July 1995 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Proposal for Project Management Services Seventh and Penn Project by the Galbreath Company, July 1995 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Proposal for the Performance of Program Management Services Seventh and Penn Project by O'Brien-Kreitzberg, July 1995 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Proposal for the Study of the Financial Health of Arts Organizations in the City of Pittsburgh by the Pennsylvania Economy League, October 1987 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Proposal to Davy International for 174,944 Square Feet of Premier Office Space in the Tower at Theater Square by Oliver Tyrone Pulver Corporation, January 1996 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Proposal to Federated Investors for the Federated Investors Building at Theater Square by Oliver Tyrone Pulver Corporation, July 1993 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Proposal to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust for Construction Management Services Allegheny Riverfront Park by Oxford Development Company, July 1995 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Proposal to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust for Exclusive Leasing Services by Pennsylvania Commercial Real Estate Inc, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Proposal to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust for Program Management Services Seventh and Penn Project by Oxford Development Company, July 1995 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Proposal to Transarc Corporation for the Tower at Theater Square by Oliver Tyrone Pulver Corporation, October 1997 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Public brochure, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Public document - comments on draft, August 1990 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Public improvements plan map, July 1998 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Public report - draft, August 1990 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Public report - final, 1990-1992 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Qualifications and Fee Proposal to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust for Allegheny Riverfront Park by Jendoco Construction Corporation, July 1995 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Rax, 1989-1991 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Real Estate Appraisal - century Building 130-134 Seventh Street Second Ward City of Pittsburgh Allegheny County Pennsylvania by Diversified Evaluation Company (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Recycling, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Rent calculations / building budgets, 1993 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Report of available commercial space in downtown Pittsburgh by Pennsylvania Commercial Real Estate (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Request for Proposal for Program Management Services Seventh and Penn Project by the Poli and Cuteri architects, July 1995 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Response to Request for Proposals - Historic Rehabilitation and Adaptive Reuse Building at 900 Penn Avenue Penn-Liberty Historic District Pittsburgh's Cultural District by Ralph A. Falbo Inc., May 1997 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Revenue projections, 1991-1993 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Riverfront park ceremonial dedication, November 1998 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Riverfront park design team selection committee, July 1994 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Riverfront park development, 1993-1994 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Riverfront park planning, 1987-1988 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Robert H. Lurcott receipts, 1989-1993 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Safety issues, 1993-1994 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Schematic Estimate - Byham Theatre's Box Office Addition & Exterior Facade by Crawford Consulting Services,1998 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Script for slide show presentation (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Seattle group presentation, May 1990 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Seventh Street Parking Garage Feasibility Study by Kingsland Scott Bauer Havekotte Architects, August 1987 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Street Parking Garage Feasibility Study by Kingsland Scott Bauer Havekotte Architects, September 1987 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Street Parking Garage Feasibility Study by Kingsland Scott Bauer Havekotte Architects, October 1987 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Street Parking Garage Private Financing Alternatives Analysis by Marguerite Brogan Real Estate Consulting Services (draft), March 1992 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Seventh Street parking garage special structural conditions by Kingsland Scott Bauer Havekotte Architects, November 1987 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Seventh / Penn Century Building, 1986-1989 (Box 127, Folder 6-8)
    - Seventh / Penn garage, September 1986 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Seventh / Penn garage, 1986-1990 (Box 128, Folder 1-5)
    - Seventh / Penn Pages condominium, 1986 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Seventh / Penn Pages condominium, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Seventh / Penn Stabile lots purchase, 1986-1987 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Seventh / Penn schedules, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Seventh / Penn site predevelopment expenses, 1992-1993 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Sewers, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Shared cost allocation, 1993 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Site area calculations, 1991 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - S.I.P. proposals for movie complex, July 1990 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Slide materials and p.r.,1992 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Speeches and presentations, 1989 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Speeches and presentations, 1991 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Stabile / Seventh Street Property Development Analysis by Kingsland Scott Bauer Havekotte Architects, July 1987 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Stanley Theater project - open space settlement, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - State Funding, 1989-1990 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - State Funding, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - State funding materials, 1991-1993 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Strategic rehabilitation, 1994 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Streetscape program, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Technical Memorandum Stanley Theatre Management Structure by Economic Research Associates and Brannigan-Lorelli Associates, October 1983 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Technical Memorandum an Update of Audience Market Studies for the Pittsburgh Performing Arts District by Economic Research Associates, November 1985 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Technical Proposal Marketing and Economic Feasibility Penn / Liberty Preservation Study by Hammer Siler George Associates, January 1986 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Tenet materials, 1991-1994 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Theater Square Project Pittsburgh Cultural District by Dick Group of Companies, April 1993 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Theater Square Construction Management Services Interview by Oliver Tyrone Pulver Corporation, July 1993 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Theater Square Project Construction Management Services by P.J. Dick Incorporated and Oliver Tyrone Pulver Corporation, May 1993 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Theater Square Parking Facility by Mulach Parking Structures Corporation, April 1993 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Trafalgar House Construction (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Traffic and parking, 1990-1993 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - UDAG Benedum capital budget and reports, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 3-4)
    - UDAG Benedum construction, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - UDAG Benedum foundation reports 1 and 2, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 6-7)
    - UDAG Benedum summary reports, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - UDAG CNG Tower and Benedum project invoices, 1985-1987 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - UDAG grant materials, 1983-1988 (Box 134, Folder 3-4)
    - UDAG reports, 1993-1998 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - UDAG reports estimated personnel costs, 1988-1998 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - UDAG report with Benedum backup, 1997-1998 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - URA/UDAG, 1984-1990 (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
    - Urban Cleaning Services a Survey Report by the Atlantic Group, January 1994 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Utility issues, 1991-1994 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Valuation of land, 1994 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Victory Building, 1986-1990 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Walker parking consultants parking garage feasibility study, 1991-1992 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Water, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 3)